Tod's father called.
They'll pick you up tomorrow at 3:30, the bus leaves around 5.
—Was my suitcase enough for you? —No, you have to leave that.
I've already flown with that tag without anything happening,
so I'd say it's better if it stays attached to the suitcase.
-Let's say it brings luck. -Where does such a stupid idea come from?
Well, I'm still alive.
17 years old, a 10-day trip to Paris with
school friends, without parents, in spring...
Enjoy it, Alex. Life is all yours.
Parking is prohibited in the area marked in white.
Stopping is permitted only for loading and unloading baggage.
—Oh, Hitchcock. -What's up? -I'll give you a hand. Done.
—What an idiot.  -Good job.
-You left this above. -Thank you.
-Get your bags. -Hi, Christa. Hi, Blake.
-What are you doing? -He tries.
-So, have you taken everything? -Yes, dad.
-What did he say? To go? -I do not know.
-These are for both of us. And have fun. -Thanks Dad.
-For both. -Let's go. —Keep an eye on them. -Certain.
I didn't think I'd look worse here than in the school album photo.
Think of me seeing you every day.
What the fuck does he want?
The airport is not responsible for beggars.
Flight 406, boarding immediately.
Death is not the end.
-For you yes if you bother my students. -Hare Rama. -Fuck you.
Sorry, but I have to ask you some questions. Did you pack your bags?
Did he always have them with you or did he entrust them to someone else?
—Mr. Browning?  -No.
Wasn't she entrusted with anything by people unknown to her?
-Like her birthday. -What? -September, 25. 9 and 25.
The digits of her birthday are the same as the departure time.
What a drag.
—Dad said it's for both of us. Give me some. —Don't break.
-Give me something. -Stop that! - Get it over with. -Excuse me.
You're an idiot.
-Thank you. -Not at all.
Alex, shall we go take a shit?
-Can't you go alone? -Think. We embark on a 7 hour flight,
the toilets on the plane are lockers without ventilation.
Let's say halfway through the flight you have to unload some junk food.
Dropped 1.3kg of stuff without the parachute.
A moment later Christa or Blake enters.
Do you want them to associate their glassy, ​​horrified
gaze with that disgusted grin that curls their mouth?
He died in a plane crash.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience.
We can begin boarding operations for flight 180 to Paris.
Exit 46.
Flight 180 to Paris, immediate boarding, exit 46.
Has anyone seen Billy Hitchcock?
Go.
Go. Ouch, you hurt me.
That's a good sign, it would take a crazy God to bring this plane down.
A truly crazy God.
-HI. -Hi, Tod. -Hello, how is he doing? -Is this your place? -Yes, yours is that.
-Tod, can you change places with Christa? -Oh, damn.
Gladly, but I have a bladder problem, an infection.
-Come on, let's ask Alex. -Let's try with him.
Can you switch places with Blake so we're close? Tod doesn't want it.
-Please. -Yes.
-You are so cute. Thank you. -Thank you.
It is a pleasure.
Homosexual!
Were you convinced we were touching his tits over Greenland?
Anyway, because of you I'll have to watch Stuart Little.
Thank you, you are a friend, I love you.
-Sorry, I'm late. My place is there. -Please.
-Will you let me in? -HI. -Okay, I'll go around.
Prepare for takeoff. Illustrate the on-board safety systems.
To fasten the seat belts correctly, insert the white part
into the buckle. To unfasten them, lift the mobile part.
Prepare for takeoff.
And go!
Let's go.
Everything is fine.
Quick, put on your masks! Hurry up.
The hand.
Alex, can you switch places with Blake so we're close?
—I asked Tod, but he says he has a health problem. -Please.
We invite passengers to take their seats and fasten their seat belts.
What's happening to you?
-Is there any problem? -Yes, to the brain.
-What's up? That the plane is about to explode! -Don't shoot them.
-You are not funny. -If you want to joke, it's not funny.
-It's not a joke! -Stay calm. -Now you broke me.
-It will explode. -We'll let you off if you continue. -I'll handle that. -Take it easy.
-I'm leaving. -Stay still. - Leave him.
-Sorry, that's my place. -Let me get off. - Leave him.
-He had nothing to do with it. -The plane will explode! -Stay in your seats.
It will explode. You all have to get out.
Go and see what they do to him.
-I did nothing. -Take your hands off me. -Stop it, idiot.
-Floor. —So, is that clear? These do not go back on board. —And leave me.
Wait, I have 40 guys going to Paris, please.
-I know, but understand my position. -I understand, but one of us has to go up,
we cannot leave them in Paris without teachers. -Carter, no!
Just stand there.  Stay there!
One of you can get back up, no one else.
Last call for flight 371 to London. Immediate boarding.
The airline picks up one of us.
The others can take the 11am flight, it will arrive...
-I'll stay. -No, you speak French, take it yourself, it's better.
I was in the bathroom and the door got stuck and I couldn't...
Wait, I didn't argue with anyone. What a drag.
Thank you.
I called your parents, they're on their way.
Goodbye Paris.
-Tell me. Tell me what happened. -I saw it.
I saw it on the runway, I saw it take off.
—From the window I could see the lights of the airport. -No, Carter.
The fuselage begins to shake and the left side breaks.
And the whole plane explodes. It was so real, like it was really happening.
-Have you been on many planes that have exploded? -You must have fallen asleep.
They kicked us off the plane, we lost half a day in Paris and
just because he had a bad dream?! The plane is about to explode!
—Stop it! —You make the trip to the hospital.
Alex, stop it!
He goes away and we stay.
-You pay for this. -I wish you were on the plane. You bad ass!
Oh, fuck!
You look at me like it's my fault.
I have nothing to do with it.
Are there any survivors?
I do not know.
-You think I'm some kind of.. .-he's not a sorcerer.
I'm Howard Segal, Transportation Security Agency.
We have warned your parents, they are coming.
Meanwhile, is there anyone who needs medical or spiritual assistance?
What happened? Are there any survivors?
The cause of the explosion is still unspecified.
The county authorities are at work, the searches continue,
let's hope that... -Excuse me. I'm Agent Weine, this is Agent Schreck.
We're FBI. I can imagine how you feel and I know it
won't be easy, but we have to ask you some questions,
while the memories are still fresh.
They will certainly be useful for rescue operations and judicial investigations.
You said, "You have to get off, the plane is about to explode."
-How did you know? -I had a feeling.
-A strange feeling. -Did you take any sedatives before boarding?
Once on board, you took sleeping pills, narcotics, hallucinogens...
-Have you taken drugs? -No. I saw it.
I saw the plane explode.
Does the strange feeling have anything to do with what you said?
That you wanted Carter Horton to be on that plane before it exploded?
-Then why did you say that? -I didn't think it would really happen.
If so, why did you want to get off the plane?
My brother George told me to see what happened to Alex.
So he stayed...
He told me to get off the plane.
Larry Murnau said he wanted to stay, but I told
him he had to go. I sent him back on the plane.
So, they didn't force you to leave the plane, you
said you weren't friends with those who got off,
can you explain to us why you came down?
Because I saw and heard Alex.
And I believed him.
—Oh, God, Alex!  —A|ex, my son.
Oh, Terry, my child.
-There he is. -How are you?
Thanks for the ride.
This is the first piece to reach the shore of the wreckage of Flight 180,
which exploded shortly after take-off at 9.25pm ​​from JFK in New York.
At the moment there are no survivors.
The efforts of the coast guard and rescue teams continue,
despite the difficulties caused by the burning fuel patches.
The authorities say they are pessimistic about the possibility
of finding any survivors. They are all presumed dead.
Among them, 40 students and 4 teachers
who had gone on a school trip to Paris.
Some students were reportedly dropped off before takeoff.
The authorities prefer not to say too much about the causes.
Investigators from the Transportation Security Agency and
the FBI arrived at the airport to begin the investigation.
Eyewitnesses reported seeing the plane explode.
At the time, no other aircraft were visible near Flight 180.
The airport and air traffic controllers confirm the witnesses' version.
After the explosion fragments would have rained into the Atlantic.
It has been 39 days since we lost our 39 friends and teachers. And
every day that passes without knowing the causes of the disaster
we ask ourselves: why?
Ecclesiastes tells us: "Man does not even know
his time, like fish caught in the fatal net,
or birds caught in a snare...
Like these, the man is surprised by the misfortune that suddenly
befalls him. And so in order to heal and escape the presence of death,
we must cry and remember them with this monument.
Don't think I'm grateful just because my name isn't on there.
-At all. -If I have a debt, it is with them.
-Live my life to the fullest. -Then stay away from alcohol.
Don't tell me what to do. I control my life, not you.
I will never die.
Hey, Alex, listen. The other day I went to take the driving test.
I got a 70, which is a poor score, but I passed.
When I finish the exam, you know the guy in the car who examines you?
-Certain. -He said to me: "Young man, you will die very young."
Well, is it true?
Not now and not here.  He is excluded.
-If I ask Silvia Paster out, will she say no? -Fuck.
-Okay.  -Already.  -Already.
—Mrs Lewton? -Please, it terrifies me to hear you talk.
Excuse me.
-HI. -HI.
Don't get any strange ideas, but I miss you. Really.
Yes, you too.
-But my father doesn't understand, you know. -Already.
Once he gets over this, we'll get the car
and we go to town to watch the Yankees. -Yes, certainly.
I'd better go. Lewton had given me some material in
class, I'll read that. She tells how I feel inside.
We will see each other.
It's thanks to you that I'm still alive.
Thank you.
We say that the time of death cannot be predicted.
But when we say this, we imagine that
hour lies in a dark and distant future.
The idea that it has a connection with the day that has begun does not even remotely occur to us.
Or that death may come this very afternoon.
This afternoon that seems so certain to us,
which has every hour already established and programmed.
The Lakers have a solid lead at this point.
What happened?  Where's Tod?
Go away.
-You didn't see it coming. -What happened?
You had triggered such guilt in Tod for
leaving George that he committed suicide.
He would never have done it.
He said we'd see each other again when he got over her.
Why would he tell me these things if he was thinking of killing himself?!
Come on, close.  We can go.
—It's almost autumn. —We are still in June.
Yes, but everything is always in transition.
If you concentrate, even now that it's summer you can feel autumn.
-I like being able to see the future. -Why were you outside Tod's house yesterday?
I've watched enough TV to know that the FBI doesn't investigate teen suicides.
If they were there yesterday, it means that:
1) they don't know what caused the disaster 2) they don't rule anything out.
The fact that 7 people got off the plane is undoubtedly strange.
If you then add that one of those had a vision of the plane exploding
shortly before it actually exploded, it's pretty suspicious.
And the fact that the visionary's friend just committed suicide doesn't help.
Why were you there last night?
-Do you know what this is? -It's a...
-Who is this glass head? -It's you.
It's not a portrait, it's how you make me feel.
-I am sorry. -Like you, this sculpture doesn't really know what it is and why.
He refuses to take shape and at the same time
creates a strong, but incomprehensible attraction.
In four years of school we never said a word to each other.
But at some point on the plane I felt what you felt.
I didn't understand where those emotions
came from until you started acting crazy.
I didn't see what you saw, but I felt it too.
You I still try, don't you? Something from that day is still inside you.
I know because I keep hearing you.
That's why I was there last night.
It's the first time I've dealt with death.
It could all be in our heads.
-But the feeling is that it is around us. -Meaning what?
What if Tod had just been the first of us?
-Is that something you feel? -I don't know. If at least I could see him again,
one last time, I would know maybe.
So, let's go to him.
It is exciting.
-This place? -Doing something we shouldn't do.
Let's go.
-And he? -I believe. Why did they make him up like Michael Jackson?
Yes, it's him, but there's nothing left of Tod except his body.
Christ!
Shh, please, you will wake the dead man.
-Why did he move? -Chemical substances.
Introducing them into the vascular system can cause spasms.
-Look, I'm a friend of his... -I know who you are.
How do you explain all those signs?
-Skin tears from pulling the thread. -For pulling the thread?
So he didn't want to kill himself, it was an accident.
In death there are no accidents, no coincidences, no setbacks.
And there are no loopholes.
What you need to understand is that we are
all little mice held by the tail by a cat.
Our every gesture, action, from the most banal to the
most noble, the red light at which we stop or not,
the people we have sex with or not,
the planes we travel on and get off,
everything is part of Death's sadistic plan, which leads to the grave.
A drawing?
Does that mean that if you understand the plan you can fool Death?
You already did it when you got off that plane.
Your friend's end proves that Death has a new plan for you.
So now you have to figure out when and how she will come back for you.
Use your intuition if you want to try to get out of it.
But keep in mind the risk of blowing up the plan, of
not adapting to the plan. You might go on a rampage
that would terrify even the grim reaper.
And there's no point pissing off that old slut.
Agree. So, sorry for the inconvenience.
No disturbances.  No excuses.
We will see each other soon.
Did you understand? He said that Death has a plan.
Let's talk about omens.
What do we know that by sitting here or drinking coffee, or breathing,
or crossing on the stripes we have started a chain of events
that will lead us to death in 40 years, or 10 years, or tomorrow?
We don't know.
Unless we are ready to understand the signs that are sent to us.
I don't understand, did you see Tod die? Did it happen again?
-Like on a plane? -No, I didn't see it, but it was basically the same.
This is the message of something, or someone
which suggests a design. -All bullshit.
You can find the omens wherever you want.
Caffè begins with C and ends with E for corpse.
Does that mean that if you drink it you'll end up dead? Come on, what do you say?
We go crazy with this bullshit.
That guy said Death has a plan, right?
So what if I, you, Tod, Carter, Terry,
Billy, Lewton had ruined that plan?
Suppose I managed to see Death's plan, we fooled him.
But what if that was our time? What if we didn't have to save ourselves?
What if it were our turn again? In this case nothing would have ended.
And we will all die. Now, not for who knows how long.
Unless we figure out the pattern and screw her again.
Hearing what you say, that certainly is the case.
Tod committed suicide.
Come on, let him go.
-Carter. -So there's some kind of meeting. -Let it be.
-How long until you move? -A couple of weeks. -What a pity.
-Carter, asshole. -The best teacher is leaving. -Let's go.
-I have to tell you something important. -Has she been here all her life? -Yes.
-And now she will change city. -Are you listening to me? You are all in danger!
Stop! They are dead and we are alive. Go on.
I don't accept a plane crash as the most important thing in my life!
I'll move on.
And if you want to waste your life fighting with
Alex when you see him, then you better go to hell!
-Ready? -Ready? Is Alex there? —Hi, Claire. Yes, one minute.
It's Claire again, do you want to talk to her?
-He's in the shower, shall I call you back? -Thank you. Good evening.
She's worried about you. I'm worried too.
Why don't you want to talk to her? Or with me?
You and Mom are helping me a lot, but there's something I
need to understand before I can talk to anyone about it.
Now the other news. The Transportation Safety Board has a new
theory about the possible cause of the explosion on Flight 180.
Experts believe that deterioration of the silicone insulation
of an electrical connector of the drain pump may have caused it
a spill of flammable liquids. —It's Tod's place.
A spark would have ignited the fuel in the pipeline which,
proceeding to the pump, would have caused the explosion.
The path of the explosion.
First was Tod, then there was Terry.
They are dying in the order they were supposed to die. This is the drawing.
Next is Lewton.
And as soon as I get to sleep I see Terry Cheney.
During the day, suddenly, I hear my voice in my ears
saying to Larry Murnau: "You speak French, take the plane."
Everything reminds me of that evening.
Of course, in fact I hope that the change can help.
I've spent my whole life here, you know?
Everything so far had been so wonderful.
But now I only see Larry and all my boys.
Even looking at the lawn in front of the house terrifies me, it distresses me.
Laura, I'll call you back later. Certain.
Fuck.
I'm Valery Lewton, I'd like Agent Schreck.
-What are you doing here? -Nothing.
I was checking if the wheels were okay.
Get in the car.
Put on your seatbelt.
I think it's Professor Lewton's turn now.
-It's your turn? -It's up to her, why
there is a pattern that develops. -Yeah, you noticed it too, right?
Mom's favorite.
Explain this pattern to me, does this also come from one of your visions?
Or is there some other new story?
I didn't ask for that vision. And you're making fun of me.
Okay, I'm in, but I saved 6 lives on that plane.
And the reward is that the whole school thinks he's crazy.
I don't suffer from post-traumatic stress or an omnipotence complex
and I won't act crazy, I guarantee it. I'll tell you what it is.
There is a pattern, a plan for everyone.
There is a plan for her, and for her. There's a design for everyone
and I don't know how yet, but I'm going to blow this one up.
At first you were under scrutiny because you were suspected for the explosion.
Now, I know you didn't do it, we were about to let you go,
but then the other survivors began to die.
First your friend Tod, then Terry and you were there at the scene of the death.
And tonight we find you at Valery Lewton's.
No one has control over life and death,
unless he himself takes the life.
—Now can you promise me that no one else will die? -No, I can not.
As long as I'm here, I'm out of the game, sorry.
All right, go, get out of here.
Thank you.
—That boy gives me shivers. —We have nothing to hold him.
That's not what I was talking about. There were times when...
Which I was about to believe him.
Don't blame me, but sometimes you make me shiver.
You have to stop it. Calm down, she's just a stupid herbal tea. You're out of it.
You'll be leaving soon.
Professor Lewton!
Now you mustn't move, okay?
Oh God!
Fuck.
—No, I don't know where it is. She stopped talking to me. -Why?
-Because I didn't believe him. -If she called you, she would be in your best interest
let us know, for your safety. Here is my phone.
It's a toll-free number.
Interesting job.
Carter, are you crazy?!
What are you doing?
Terry's name must be here too.
Fuck! Why did you want us to meet here?
Because they're watching me to see if I go to Alex.
-So you'll take me there. -Why should I go to him?
Because he knows who will die next.
Do you mind not going over the limit? Oh, also don't overtake on the right.
Billy, I have a vision.
-You'll be next. -Why? -If you say another word, I'll kill you.
He should be around here, you go forward a mile then come back.
I will come to meet you, so we save time.
Do you believe they are up there?
That somehow Flight 180 is still up
there, in a place where everyone is okay?
When I was a child I was so worried that my parents would die.
-I spent the nights awake with that fear. -It happens to many children.
But parents usually don't die.
I was 10 years old, my father went out to buy cigarettes.
Someone told him: "Don't turn around" and he instinctively, or
thinking of a joke, turned around. And he shot him in the head.
Since then life has been shit. My mother never recovered.
She remarried some asshole she wouldn't have
even looked at if my father had still been alive.
He didn't want children and my mother didn't want any more either.
If this was the plan for my
father and my family, screw Death.
I thought about it a lot, that place exists.
There is a place where my father feels good, where
that evening he bought cigarettes and went home.
Where my mother, my father and I are together and we
don't give a damn about the life we ​​live down here.
Where our friends are still on that plane.
Where everyone has a second chance.
We must not give up.
I can't go home because after the Lewtons die they'll be looking for me.
We'll take you to my father's little house near my house.
So Browning, you fucking fortune teller, did you already know about Lewton or not?
And why did he hide me, in your opinion?
Billy told the FBI that he saw you run away from the house.
I ran away because they blame me for everything: for Tod, for her
and also for the plane. -The fire has caramelized the blood.
There were prints from your shoes, fingerprints on the knife.
-I told you. -The problem isn't whether it was you
and not even if you knew she was dead.
Did you know it was her turn before it happened?
Yes, I knew it.
So, among us, who's next?
Please tell me I'll get to see the Jets win a Super Bowl.
It's me, right?  That's why you shut up.
Well, I knew I had to feel Tammy's tits that time.
-What are you whining?! I'm next. -He didn't say anything. Guide.
—You have to tell me. —Do you think it's easier if you know?
-On the contrary, it will be much harder. -You enjoy keeping me on my toes.
-Let me decide how to deal with it. -It doesn't matter whose turn it is.
We are all on the same list.
Oh, fuck!  Really?
Why am I worried? Terry and I will meet again on the other side anyway.
Why wait any longer?
Carter, what are you doing?
-Carter, slow down! -'Fuck you!
-Stop that! -Why? At least if I stay there, I will have decided it.
Not with us in the fucking car!
Christ, turn right!
-Stop! -What the fuck are you worried about? It's not your time anyway.
—Even if I kill myself, what do you care? It's up to me anyway. -It does not work like that.
And I hated French class.
-You need to take back control. -That's what I do. -I know,
It's normal to be afraid. -I'm not afraid, I decide when the time is!
-I control my life and even my death. -You don't have to prove it to us.
-Stop driving like a dickhead! -What are you doing? -Stop that!
What the fuck are you doing?! Put your hands back on the wheel.
Hands on the wheel!
-Get it over! -If I start vomiting, I'll flood your car.
We are afraid too, but we will not give up. Stop!
Holy shit, do you want to stop this car?!
-Move it. -Open the door. -Move this fucking car!
-Open the door. -Start it. -Hurry up, open the door.
-You can not. -You open! -Move. -You open!
Listen to me, don't do it.
-Are you crazy? Come down, come on! -Carter, listen to me.
-This is not the way. You go out! -Is coming.
It's not my time.
-Fuck. -Trust me, this is not the way, get out of the car.
-You go out! -Let's go! Jump out!
I can't get out!
Then it's really her turn.
-After you! -Get away from there! -Fuck!
-Oh, God. -I saw it. I had seen the belt.
-Do you believe him now? -It's broken. -What are you saying?
-He saved your life again, asshole. -Are you next?
-I'm miles away from you. -Shut up. -Do not say these things.
-This is the reality: he's next, stay away from him. -'Fuck you.
But you will die, you are dead. You are dead!
And don't take me with you!
-Christ! -He It was your turn, that was the plan, that was the plan.
-You should have died. -Who the fuck are you? The devil? -I saw the belt.
I knew she was broken. This is how I saved him, like with the plane,
with the explosion, I saw it. -Let's leave. -Fuck, I saved him!
So, he skipped over Carter and went to the next guy, Billy.
I have to see it. If I see it, then I intervene and thus screw up the drawing.
-Are you intervening? Are you God now? -I'm not afraid of dying!
-The gods do not die. We die, understand? -What are you saying?
The police are coming, let's go to my father's house.
—You hide there and think about it as much as you want. -After Billy it's my turn.
-And then mine. -Listen, I'll make sure it doesn't happen, okay?
-Trust me. —You two better get out of the way now.
Rusty.  Tetanus.
Ingenious, I hadn't thought of that.
You wanted to be clever, but it went badly for you, right?
I can beat you.
Not forever, but I've prepared this house to beat you now!
—It was there until a minute ago. -What are you talking about?
I'm not handing him over to you, but he runs too many risks out there alone.
-I'll accompany you. -Is excluded.
Just tell us where he is. I give you my word that
we will take Him safely, into protective custody.
I didn't move.
Christa had asked to change seats, but I didn't move.
I had forgotten. Claire was sitting in front of me.
It's your turn.
Stop, get in the car, let's go around. Let's go!
-Over there! -Let's go, come on!
We want to help you.
Rex, don't come closer!
Let's go.
Run!
-Disappeared. -Given the direction it can only go to one place. -Oh, no!
Don't move, stay there!
Don't touch anything, the tires isolate you.
The car will explode.
There's only one thing to do, I have to take your place.
If I do, Death will leap at you and it will be over.
-It's the only way to screw her again. -No, don't.
I don't let him take both you and me, you know what to do.
I'll always be with you.
Alex, get out of there!
Answer me, you can't do this to me.
-Come on, please! -A|ex, can you hear me?
Oh, shit, he's not breathing! Come on, Alex, don't leave.
-We have arrived. -Paris, I can't believe it.
I can't believe I got back on a plane. You understand me, don't you?
But it's strange to be here. Finally completed the puzzle.
Even if something is missing.
-To Terry. -Yes, to Tod. -To all our friends who are not here.
-To them.  -To them.
-What's up? -If they had told me 6 months ago
that the three of us would be sitting here drinking... -Yeah.
I mean, sometimes I feel like you two are the only ones who really understand.
You were right, he skipped us. There was a drawing.
And we screwed him.  We won.
We just won the chance to live a full life.
-And I don't want to waste it. -Already.
-There's just something that doesn't add up to me. -Would be?
—The drawing. - Leave it alone, please. —Listen to me.
-OMG! -Listen.
The path of the explosion determined the order of deaths.
When I stepped in to save Carter, he got
jumped and it was the next guy's turn, Billy.
And then there was Claire. But I intervened and it was my turn.
But in my case, no one intervened, right?
I was thrown away from the cable by the explosion, so...
-Why did he skip you? -Because perhaps this was our destiny.
Maybe of all those on Flight 180, you, Carter, and I were meant to live.
-This was most likely the drawing. -Or you're still next.
-Stop that. -Why? I didn't make the rules.
Someone has to intervene for Death to jump you, Alex
proved it three times: on the plane, with me, with you.
For all I know, the round could start again, but I
feel like I'm in a bind, because you're still first.
Shall we stop with this talk? Let's talk about what we're going to do here.
-See you later at the hotel, okay? -Wait, I'll accompany you. -No.
You stay here. You have to stay here, it's better.
-See it's true, I told you that you're next. -Stop that.
-Wait! -No, stay there, okay? She stays away.
-I told you it was your turn. -Then she jumped me.
And who's next?